https://www.intercompcompany.com/privacy-policy

WORLDWIDE: +1-763-476-2531
View Quote Cart (0)
Data Collection
Enforcement (Portable)
Enforcement (In-Ground)
Ports/Gates
Tolling (ETC)
Privacy Policy
Effective: January 1, 2013	Intercomp Company is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site and will not sell or provide any non-public personal information to anyone without your permission. Types of Information
Cookies.A Cookie is a randomly generated unique number placed on your computer. It allows us to identify your computer without requiring your disclosure of any Non-Public Personal Information. Cookies make it possible to both store and retrieve information through your internet browser. A Cookie itself cannot read information off a hard drive or read Cookie files from other sites. General Informationis information that does not itself reveal your identity. General Information may include, without limitation: generic business type; SIC code; information derived from publicly available databases (such as Dun and Bradstreet); user behavior on our Web site; and aggregated generic information. Non-Public Personal Informationis any non-public information you provide to us or our Partners that is proprietary or identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you or someone at your business. Non-Public Personal Information may include, without limitation: name; address; phone number; e-mail address; credit card number; account information; voting behavior; spending patterns; and individual tastes and preferences. Partnersare individuals or entities we engage to help us carry out our mission. What Information We Collect	Intercomp Company collects general information and non-public personal information. How We Collect Our Information	Intercomp Company collects our general information through the use of cookies and server-based tracking systems to view the usage of the website.	Non-public personal information is collected through registration or contact forms on this site and will never be used for any purpose other than internal use or by our partners unless the registrant chooses to be added to mailing lists (this is a choice made by the registrant on the Registration form). Privacy Policy Changes	Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted here and unless otherwise noted on our website. Changing Your Non-Public Personal Information	Intercomp Company provides you with the opportunity to change your non-public personal information online for all registration information. Please contact Intercomp Company to change any non-public personal information provided to us through a contact form.	If you have any questions or concerns about any privacy issues, please contact us.
Home
About Us
Contact Us
Latest News:
Intercomp RFX® Wireless Corner Balancing Scale Systems
Intercomp Introduces First Wireless Load Stick to Racing Market
Enforcement (Portable)
Enforcement (In-Ground)
Ports/Gates
Tolling (ETC)
Enforcement (Portable)
Enforcement (In-Ground)
Ports/Gates
Tolling (ETC)
Rim Clamp - Auto (13 to 18"/330 to 457 mm)
Rim Clamp - Truck (16 to 25"/406 to 635 mm)
Enforcement (Portable)
Enforcement (In-Ground)
Ports/Gates
Tolling (ETC)
View Quote Cart (0)
©  Intercomp's Worldwide Headquarters | 3839 County Road 116 | Medina, MN 55340-9342 USA
Toll Free (US Canada): 800-328-3336 | Worldwide: +1 763-476-2531 | Fax: +1 763-476-2613
